偷Han的碟子
Stealing Han's dishes
那么咱们在家就不用洗了 这真是天才
so we don't have to clean ours at home is genius.
可是又有点悲催啊
and a little sad.
你说笑的吧?
Are you kidding?
这是今早我大姨妈来了以后
This is the greatest thing that's happened to me
最令人舒畅的事情了
since I got my period this morning.
Max Caroline 你们在偷我的碟子?
Max, Caroline, you're stealing my dishes?
该死 没想到这么高你还看得到
Damn it, I didn't think you could see up this high.
我也没想到你们的底线已经如此之低
And I didn't think you could sink this low.
好了 够了 我已经被你们的
Okay, stop, you're already robbing me blind
"我是服务员"的把戏骗过我了
with your "I'm a waitress" scam.
不好意思 但是我们家乱得要死
Sorry, but things have gotten kind of messy at home.
昨天 我还得再洗一次澡
Yesterday, I had to take a shower
冲掉自己因为洗澡而沾上的脏东西
to shower off the shower I took.
你们应该找个清洁工
You two should get a cleaning lady.
我雇了个女的打扫我公寓
I have a woman I pay to clean my apartment.
价格很贵 不过可能你们会便宜点
She is expensive, but she may charge you less
如果用不着陪你们上床的话
if you don't also have sex on her.
我帮你们联系一下
I'll look into it.
我奶奶打扫房间都免费的
My grandmother cleaned the house free of charge.
当然她也没啥权利谈报酬
Of course she didn't have a say in the matter.
直接找Sophie吧 她开家政公司的
Let's just ask Sophie. She has a cleaning service.
一定得想想办法了
We have to do something.
昨天 我在家里都看到蟑螂了
Yesterday, I saw a roach walk out of our apartment.
听着
Look.
我准备和你说话 正如
I'm gonna tell you what I told that guy
我对那个利用我的屁股运毒的家伙一样
who asked me to use my butt to smuggle opium.
好的!
I'll do it!
--==圣城家园SCG字幕组  http://hd.cnscg.com/ ==--
仅供翻译交流使用, 禁止用于商业用途
协调: 。沫
时间轴:  桃茜茜
翻译:  Mabb 桃茜茜
校对: 桃茜茜
准备好 Max
Be ready, Max.
清洁工一来 我们就要走了
We have to leave as soon as the cleaning lady gets here.
这是房主表示礼貌的方式
It's housekeeper etiquette.
在从前 我会去上刺绣课 然后和朋友吃午饭
In my old life, I go to spin class and lunch with friends,
现在嘛 咱俩就出门
but you and I will just go outside
去瞧瞧那些刚出狱的犯人
and watch the guy who just got out of jail
在灯柱上做引体向上
do pull-ups on the light post.
Calvin出来了?
Calvin's out?
我才不走呢
I'm not gonna leave.
我要看着她打扫房子
I want to watch her clean up my mess.
耶 来呀
Yeah, baby.
我这一直想着有个女仆呢
I've waited my whole life to have a servant.
你刚来的时候 我以为你可以给我当女仆
I thought you were gonna be it for the first few weeks
后来发现你啥都不会干
and then I realized you can't do anything.
虽然Sophie给我们打了折
And even though Sophie gave us a discount,
女仆还是得管我叫"女王殿下"
The maid still has to call me "your highness."
主要因为我现在确实是女王上身
Mostly because I'm pretty "highness" right now.
嗨 姑娘们
Hi, girls.
我来了
Here I am.
我是"苏菲的抉择"家政服务的Sophie
Sophie from Sophie's choice cleaning service.
这位是你们的清洁工Pauline
Meet your cleaning lady Paulina.
Paulina 打个招呼
Paulina, meet the girls.
嗯
Mm.
她想握手来着 但是她只有一只胳膊
She'd shake hands, but she only has one arm.
Sophie 当面说不好吧
Sophie, she can hear you.
怎么了? 我知道我少了只胳膊
So what? I know I'm missing arm.
又不是什么新闻
It's not news.
她丢了胳膊
So she lost an arm.
我在垃圾桶丢了金耳环
I lost my gold earring down the garbage disposal
但我不敢去捡回来
but I was too afraid to reach into it
因为 你懂的
because, well, yeah.
别担心
Don't worry.
虽然少了只胳膊 我干起活来就像有三只手
I have one arm but I clean like I have three.
我去补下妆 然后就开始
I put on more makeup, then I start.
不好意思
I'm sorry.
我没想到 找个清洁女工之时
I didn't realize when I ordered a cleaning lady
我得特别申明要双臂健全的
I had to specify I wanted one with two arms.
两只手的你请不起啊
You can't afford two arms.
你说了要特价的
You said you wanted a good price.
半残半价
Half the arms, half the price.
她因为这活儿而丢掉一只手的吗 Sophie
Is that how she lost the arm, Sophie?
你为了给我们特价 把她胳膊砍了?
You cut it off so we could get a discount?
哦 当然 没错
Oh, yeah, sure.
为了帮你们省十块钱 我把她胳膊锯掉了
Yeah, I sawed off her arm so I could save you 10 bucks.
我先从卧室开始
I start in bedroom.
等一下 先让我问个问题
Wait, before you do, one question.
你这胳膊是怎么没的 就像詹姆斯·弗兰科那样吗?
How'd you lose it? James Franco situation?
为了逃命而把它砍掉?
You had to cut it off to get loose?
你没否认哦
You're not saying no.
好啦 别提这个了
Oh, you know what, let's not go there.
过去的 就让它过去吧
You know, it happened, it was in the past.
我当时被一辆大货车给困住了
I was trapped under this big truck.
我们都知道了
We get it.
是我开车碾了你胳膊
I drove over your arm.
嘿 别想从屋里偷我的珠宝
Hey, don't even bother looking for my good jewelry in there
因为我全戴着呢
because I'm already wearing all of it.
好嫉妒你啊 我都没有胳膊来戴这些地摊货
Oh, I'm jealous I don't have arm to wear cheap jewelry.
Max 我于心不忍
Max, I feel bad for her.
明白了吧? 所以你要离开
See? This is why you leave.
避免碰到女佣妆太浓
In case they show up with too much makeup
而胳膊又太少的情况
and not enough arms.
别紧张 她很坚强
Relax, she's tough.
让我想起了年轻时候的自己
Reminds me of a young me.
这意味着我得把药都藏好
Which means I better go hide my pills from her.
Max 她吓着我了
Max, she scares me.
别这样 她只是少胳膊
Oh, come on, she's armless.
还好吧?
Everything okay?
需要帮忙吗?
You need any help?
我取得今日的行业地位 可不是靠别人的帮助
I didn't get this far in this business by taking help.
搭把手啊 看不见我只有一只胳膊吗?
Help me! Can't you see I got one arm?
没问题
Not gonna be a problem.
我偶尔也会帮帮我的女仆...
I would occasionally help my maid...
你没兴趣
You're not interested.
抬起来!
Lift!
抬啊 没吃饱吗 抬
Lift, weak girl. Lift.
Max 我们在抬你的床垫
Max, come here. We need help lifting your mattress.
你能来搭把手吗?
Can you give us a hand?
不! 别碰! 别碰!
No! Leave it alone! Leave it alone!
不要抬床垫!
Don't lift up the mattress!
啊 黄书
Ah, porno.
你的思想就像房间一样肮脏!
Your mind is as dirty as your apartment!
是啊 就是黄书 有什么大不了的?
Yes, it's porn. So what? What's the big deal?
这就身体的自然状态嘛
It's just the body in its natural form,
在摩托车上摆个一字马
spread-eagle on a motorcycle.
怎么这么多八十年代的旧杂志?
Why is so much of it from the '80s?
我喜欢小胡子 不行吗?
I like mustaches, okay?
而且我还有个目的 就是看看有没我爸
And it's multitasking. I'm looking for my father.
别看了 快别看了
Stop looking. Stop looking right now.
你怎么突然这么尴尬?
Why are you suddenly embarrassed?
你的首页就是色情链接大全啊
Porn hub is your homepage.
嘿 这是糕点学校的宣传册?
Hey, is this a brochure for pastry school?
你干嘛藏着这个?
Why are you hiding a pastry school brochure?
你的脸才是糕点宣传册!
Your face is a pastry school brochure!
你对糕点学习有兴趣 这很好啊
Max, it's great you're interested in pastry school.
我不懂你有什么好尴尬的
I don't know why you're embarrassed.
你的脸才尴尬!
Your face is embarrassed!
别这样 我觉得这事情
Come on, I really think that this is
咱们应该好好谈谈
Something we should talk about.
你的脸才是我们该好好谈谈的!
Your face is something we should talk about!
你把她吓疯了
You made the scary one mad.
这么做很蠢
That was dumb move.
你的脸才蠢!
Your face was a dumb move!
Max你在吗?
Max?
Max 你狂奔出去后就没回来了
Max, you never came home after you stormed out,
我把你的工作服带来了
So I brought you your uniform.
Max什么情况?
Max?
我住这里了
I live here now.
我的新室友 扫帚和拖把
My new roommates, the broom and the mop,
它们可不会偷偷动我的东西
don't sneak around looking at my stuff.
这里什么都有
I got everything I need.
威士忌 牙刷 牙膏
Whiskey, toothbrush, toothpaste.
但是当你喝多的时候
Well, maybe your new broommate
你的扫帚室友可能会拽你头发
will hold back your hair when you drink too much.
看情况 估计一小时左右这就会发生了
Which, from the looks of it, will be in about an hour.
Max 我们真该谈谈这宣传册
Max, we really need to talk about this brochure.
听着 我有糕点学校的宣传册
Look, just because I have a pastry school brochure
不代表我想去糕点学校
doesn't mean I'm actually gonna go to pastry school.
就像我有黄色杂志
Just like having those porn magazines
不代表我会去骑着老虎跟水手
doesn't mean I'm actually gonna ride around on a tiger
一起摆出无法形容的动作 也许不会
Performing unspeakable acts with sailors, probably.
糕点学校就像黄书
Pastry school is the same as porn.
只是愚蠢的幻想
It's just a dumb fantasy.
糕点学校不是黄书
Pastry school is not like porn.
这宣传册上面
There is nothing in this brochure
完全没有两女一糕的内容
About a girl-on-girl croissant.
牙膏不错
That's good toothpaste.
请不要再刷牙了
Please stop brushing your teeth.
我们一会儿还得轮班呢
We have a shift to do later.
好了 曼哈顿糕点学校
Okay, the Manhattan school of pastry.
你的脸才是糕点学校
Your face is the manhattan school of pastry.
你知道我的脸不是
You know it isn't.
Max 你可以去的
Max, you could go here for real.
学费一年才三千 是有点多 但也能接受
Tuition is only $3,000 a year. A lot, but doable.
有点多 但能接受?
A lot but doable?
你说的是糕点学校 还是电影里的那个胖子?
Are we talking about pastry school or fat guy at Last Call?
到了 Max 这就是你梦想开始的地方
Here we are, Max. Your dream starts now.
啥? 那种吹箫不卖身的地方?
What, the one where I'm a black mermaid?
放松点行吗?
Would you relax?
我们就来看看 然后拿份申请
We're just gonna look around and get an application.
看到那些高档设备吗 如果你来上课就能用到
See all that gorgeous equipment you get to use if you went here?
你终于可以用搅拌碗了
Finally you'd have a mixing bowl
不必再用挖空的西瓜皮
that's not a hollowed-out watermelon.
帮帮我行吗?
Can you help me?
她在强迫我违背自己的意愿呢
She's holding me against my will.
开玩笑的
She's kidding.
你再这样的话 小姑娘
If you keep this up, young lady,
一会儿就不许你吃雪糕
you are not getting ice cream after.
好吧!
Fine!
来 这里是办公室
Come on, here's the office.
行了 还没完事吗?
Whatever. Are we almost done here?
我赶着上庭呢
I got a court date later.
嗨
Hi.
我们来对地方了吗?
I'm not sure we're in the right place.
谁知道我们有没来对呢?
Are any of us really?
我们想填份申请表 能帮帮我们吗?
We'd like an application. Could you help us?
哦 是啊 应该可以
Oh, god, I hope so.
我没想到第一天回到这里工作
I wasn't expecting something this high-pressure
就要处理如此高压的业务
my first day back.
我之前在精神病院留院观察
Let's just say I've been under observation at the nuthouse.
对了 申请表
Okay, application.
是给她的 这位Max
It's for Max, here.
你们的宣传册让她看了很心动
She was very impressed by your brochure.
噢 糕点学校 太棒了 对吧?
Oh, pastry school. Exciting, right?
我以前是这里的主厨 然后就不是了
I was a chef here once. And then I wasn't.
噢 瞧啊 找到申请表了
Oh, look. Found the application.
哇 真没想到我竟然做到了
Wow. Really didn't think I was gonna be able to handle that.
Bebe 如果...
Bebe, if you...
哦 你们好 早安
Oh. bonjour. good morning.
呃...
Uh...
Chef Nicolas, these girls are here for an application.
Nicolas寮놜 侶좃몸큽角윱狼헝깊돨
Don't worry, I handled it.
깎덫懃 乖못劒쳬죄
Almost didn't, then I did.
뀌듐못꼇죄 뎃乖뻘角못죄
Nice work, Bebe.
맴돤봤 Bebe
Oh, do I detect a french accent? Oui?
가 侶角랬벌왯稜찐? 羹찐?
Oh, my god, I can't watch.
莖가 꼇훠殮柬
French, indeed. I'm Chef Nicolas Saintcroix,
乖角랬벌훙 乖角寮놜Nicolas Saintcroix
Owner and head chef. Bienvenue.
角侶쟁돨랬훙쇗놜可낀 뻑短콱쳬
乖角Caroline Channing
Caroline Channing.
Is it over yet?
唐供청供가?
This is Max. The application's for her.
侶角Max 角劒狼윱헝돨
'Sup, frenchie? You eat snails?
鍛 랬벌훙 콱쳬넜卦큇?
It looks like Bebe forgot the second page.
Bebe戈션겉뒤랗女冷못콱쳬죄
Oh, boy, forgot the second page. That's not good.
莖가 乖겉뒤랗女못戈죄 侶옵痘죄
I thought I handled it. Didn't handle it.
乖鹿槨乖못죄 覩윱乖청못
It's okay, Bebe. Breathe in.
청밑溝돨 Bebe 俱폭
Breathe out.
빌폭
That's good stuff.
뻘廬밗痰
She was quite brilliant.
劒鹿품宮뎠놔돨
Then she wasn't.
횔빈劒앎꼇契죄
Here. Fill that out.
못 겉侶몸輕봤
And the next step is the pastry exam.
쌈苟윱角충빡꿎桿
Applicants will have to make a classic tart,
헝諒狼隣寧몸눈固돨彊벎軍깰
Bring them in tomorrow for me to taste,
츠莖던윱못乖끼끼
And we will go from there. Sound good?
邱앎侶湳걸 청狂痙걸?
Whatever. Maybe I'll think about it.
踞긱걸 冷冀乖삔옘쪄寧苟
Okay, well, maybe you will. Nice meeting you both.
봤걸 冷冀콱삔옘쪄 붤멕菫훰街콱쳬젤
Hope to see you tomorrow, Chef.
句寡츠莖옵鹿숨돕콱 寮놜
He called me chef!
儉싻乖寮놜!
-Yay! Let's go get ice cream!  -No!
-內! 乖쳬혼넜汽멤여 - 꼇契
You should get started on that tart.
콱壇맡邱겉彊벎軍깰隣봤
It's due tomorrow.
츠莖앎狼供냥죄
I got plenty of time.
珂쇌댕겉돨
Besides, pressure ups my game.
疼綱죄 唐듐箕제乖隣돤뫘봤
I perform my best when there's a gun to my head.
瞳굳퓜寧淪켬덟珂 乖돨깊君離봤
Ask any of my ex-boyfriends.
狂狂乖돨품켕堂쳬앎列돛죄
This is so not how I prepare for tests.
乖없뚤꼇삔侶湳硫구꿎桿돨
I studied three weeks for a pap smear.
乖隣綾묵쓩칩튬꿎桿裂품桔씩죄힛鷺
Don't worry, I got this.
깎덫懃 乖콘契돨
A tart's just like a cookie with some pudding on it, right?
彊벎軍깰앎獗角혓펜깰충속듐꼈땀 뚤걸
Max, what is going on in here?
Max 侶角等척쀼慤가
Turns out a tart's more than a cookie with some pudding on it!
覩윱彊벎軍깰꼇쏭쏭角혓펜깰충속듐꼈땀!
You've been in here six hours. You said you had this.
콱瞳侶쟁챈삶죄짇鬼珂 콱綱菱성콘契돨
I thought I had this! Turns out I don't!
乖冷鹿槨菱성콘契! 써벎角乖꼇契!
I haven't even finished a shell.
乖逞젯軍깰튄떼청隣봤
I didn't know there was a shell. Did you know there was a shell?
乖떼꼇列돛侶새唐몸軍깰튄돨 콱列돛찐?
Everybody knows there's a shell!
훙훙떼列돛唐軍깰튄돨!
What the shell is wrong with you?
콱侶軍깰튄角等척쀼慤가?
I'm a tart who can't make a tart!
乖角몸隣꼇봤彊벎軍깰돨술새!
You could've made nine shells by now.
侶삔랏콱굶맡隣봤씽몸軍깰튄죄
I did. They're all in here. Look.
乖隣죄 홍瞳侶쟁켱 콱였
It's like shell-mageddon!
侶앎獗角軍깰튄돨各썹칫휑
Oh, screw it. This one's gonna be there in a minute.
혼儉돨 侶몸寧삔랏冷삔굳돌딜돨
Let's just get it over with.
童邱苟癎槨퓻걸
No, you can do this. Here. Here.
꼇 콱옵鹿돨 법윱
This still looks ready to go.
侶욥충考챵慨옵鹿닿죄
Look at me. Look at me. I'm a waste of two arms.
픗픗乖 乖角唐좃怜癎글돨록膠
I can't make a tart!
乖꼇삔隣彊벎軍깰!
How's the tart coming?
彊벎軍깰隣돤等척湳죄?
Han, you're not safe. Leave.
Han 侶쟁꼇갛홍 먀쏨잼역
You haven't even finished the shell?
콱젯軍깰튄떼청隣봤?
That's the easiest part!
侶옵角離숌데돨가!
Han, this is your face.
Han 侶角콱돨졌뎔
Well, I should get going.
봤걸 乖먀쏨낮걸
I didn't know she could take bitch to the next level.
청拳돕劒뻘옵鹿긴돤뫘속붰뗀
I am so screwed!
乖供죄!
I finally found a situation my boobs can't get me out of!
乖老黨툭돕寧몸꼇콘옜댕禽살법밑돨헙워죄!
Hey, Max. Now, I have all the faith in the world in you.
붙 Max 乖뚤콱角斤懃찮찮돨
But here's a tart from stop 'n shop
꼇법 侶角乖닒듦쟁찜윱돨彊벎軍깰
in case you wanted to hand this one in.
콱옵鹿痰侶몸촁살법밑돨
No, Earl. Max is not a cheater.
꼇契 Earl Max꼇삔鱗그돨
Since when?
珂꼇鱗그죄?
She is going to make her own tart.
劒狼항癎隣놔寧몸彊벎軍깰
You, out.
콱 놔혼
I am never gonna make this shell.
乖없뚤隣꼇죄軍깰튄돨
I can't even get it in the pan right.
乖逞꼇콘겉충考봤봤뒈렴쏵번쟁
Max, that looks right.
Max 콱慨빎렴봤죄
Oh, my god!
莖가
I got it in the pan right! I can do this!
乖겉충考봤봤뒈렴쏵번쟁죄! 乖옵鹿죄
You did it! I knew it! I helped you. We're besties.
콱냥묘죄 乖앎列돛 角乖곤콱돨 童옵角밸쵯
You're not safe. Leave.
侶쟁꼇갛홍 먀쏨버역
I'm telling you, Max, I've tasted a lot of tarts,
乖뫄콱綱 Max 乖끼법붤뜩彊벎軍깰
and yours is delicious.
랍콱돨宮뎠봤넜가
You are not the first man to tell me that.
콱꼇角庫寧몸綱乖봤넜돨켕훙
The first man to tell me that is in jail.
庫寧몸綱侶뺐돨켕훙쏵솰掉혼죄
Here he comes.
儉윱죄
Look at him. Here he comes.
콱픗픗儉 儉윱죄
Afternoon, ladies.
큽却쳬 苟敎봤
Bien fondue, Eiffel tower.
켈잃삽번봤 갔렵랑屆檢봤
Okay.
봤돨
Thank you for coming. Shall we begin the tasting?
먁剋콱돨돕윱 乖쳬옵鹿역迦틔끼죄찐?
This is exciting, huh?
淪茄횻훙菫뢸 뚤걸?
像...
Uh...
Keep it in your pants.
꼇狼錮욍綾
And now for the tart.
윱끼끼侶彊벎軍깰
It's Max's first ever.
侶角Max庫寧쀼隣
I ate a slice earlier and it was like
乖먼꼽넜죄寧鬼욥
having a little piece of heaven.
봤넜돤獗角쏵죄莖慊
Don't do anything you're doing.
깎侶湳懃罹뎬濫
It's flaky, creamy...
붤괌 켈答뺏돤붤봤...
For a first attempt, I am very impressed.
鱗槨콱돨看늴끼桿 侶廬횻乖쑵毆
Don't be. I made a tart.
깎侶湳 乖앎角隣죄몸彊벎軍깰
It's not like I cured herpes
棠꼇角綱乖겉昑깹撈봤죄
Or invented a reverse microwave to instantly chill sodas.
샀諒角랙츠죄옵鹿醵떨폼彊돨샙포
Okay, Max.
봤죄 Max
I will talk it over with my faculty
乖삔뵨乖돨싱逃擎쬠寧苟
and we will let you know.
헝된덤乖쳬돨繫列
I'll let you know.
乖冷삔繫列콱돨
Nailed that.
멥땍죄
菅 Max
Max!
Stop stealing my things! You got a cleaning lady!
깎疼孤乖돨땜鮫 콱쳬綠쒔唐헌썅큽묏죄
Relax. I am returning what I took.
꼇狼쏨蠟 乖角瞳백뻘菱성컬돨땜鮫
Here's your plates.
侶角콱돨딪綾
Oh, and here's your atm card. I lifted it from your wallet.
킷 뻘唐콱돨陵契엥 乖닒콱돨풀관쟁컬돨
Oh, and here's your wallet.
뻘唐콱돨풀관
There was $40 in here.
侶쟁충覩굶唐愷枷욥풀돨
There sure was.
횅茄角唐
At least give me back my gift card from sephora.
逞겉介竝읊돨쟉틔엥뻘쀼못乖가
Caroline, Han wants his sephora gift card back.
Caroline Han싻콱겉介竝읊돨쟉틔엥뻘못儉
Oh, that's not happening. It's already on my face.
꼇옵콘 乖綠쒔뚝뻣냥뺏劉틔痰菱성졌죄
Max, look, it's from the pastry school.
Max 콱였 角멤듐欺叫셍윱돨
Whoo-hoo! My acceptance letter!
鍛敾! 角乖돨쩌혤繫列蝎!
Lot of people talking about my chili in that bathroom.
唐봤뜩훙瞳求癎쇌쟁擎쬠乖돨昑먁켱
Oleg, come here. Han, Earl, stay.
Oleg 법윱 Han Earl冷깎浬
You guys are about to owe me big.
콱쳬硫구댕넜寧쑵걸
I am gonna let you witness something extremely rare.
乖쉥횻콱쳬숨聯섐똥볍숨돨헙워
More rare than a sighting of bigfoot or a ufo or Han's penis.
궐랙君댕신밍 棍槿훙 샀角Han돨샷샷뻘狼볍숨
You held me here so I could hear that?
콱겉乖즛瞳侶랏 앎角槨죄횻乖桂侶뺐찐
Behold, the rarest sight of them all.
픗 侶옵廬角各쇌볍숨킷
You are about to see something good actually happen to me.
콱쳬쉥삔였돕 乖횅茄島봤慤헙죄
桂淪
Listen to this.
"Dear Ms. Black, after careful consideration
항갖돨Black鬼썬 쒔법路옘쪄
"of our large pool of applicants,
履북乖쳬댕좆헝諒돨헙워
We regret to inform you..."
乖쳬瑙볘뒈繫列콱...
Oh, I guess I didn't get in.
킷 였윱乖청굳쩌혤
Looking back, we probably should have insisted
君瞳쀼拳 冷冀乖쳬壇맡솽넣
she read that to herself first.
횻劒菱성邱뗍寧깁
I know why she didn't get in. Her name.
乖列돛劒槨청굳쩌혤 凜槨劒돨檎幹
They saw the word "black" and stopped reading.
儉쳬였돕컸몸"붚"俚 앎접쯩慶激죄
That's why I didn't get into law school.
乖앎角凜槨侶覩凜랍꼇콘뗍랬欺牘
I also didn't apply.
꼇법乖冷청唐헝
This is terrible. I'm gonna go see if she's okay.
侶廬角格痘죄 乖혼였였劒等척湳죄
Who does that French frog think he is?
컸랬벌행鵠鹿槨菱성角强가?
He thinks he can have the time of his life tasting my tart
儉鹿槨儉겉乖돨彊벎軍깰넜죄裂빈
and then never see me again?
앎옵鹿꼇疼숨乖죄찐
He won't let me into his school?
뻘꼇횻乖뗍儉돨欺叫?
Well, I won't take no for an answer.
乖꼇삔쌈肝侶蘆앳없
I am going down there right now
乖접쯩앎儉컸쟁
and giving him a piece of my mind.
횻儉숨街寧苟일쿤돨拳랬
I am storming out.
乖君瞳狼법혼죄
And I am storming back in.
乖棠쀼윱죄
It is dark outside. That school's not open.
棍충莖붚죄 欺叫밑쳔죄
Hey, you.
菅 콱
Tart tease, we need a word.
넜供孤있諒 乖唐뺐狼뫄콱綱
Oh, boy.
莖가
What?
等척?
You love my pastries
콱毆뻑乖隣돨軍깰
and then regret to inform me I'm not good enough for your school?
횔빈棠瑙볘뒈繫列乖꼇뭘목콱돨欺叫?
Well, I regret to inform you that I am good enough
乖붤瑙볘뒈繫列콱 乖렷끽뭘목
and I want to know why you won't let me in here.
乖뻘拳列돛콱槨꼇狼乖
Okay, uh, your voice is an anxiety trigger for me.
봤걸 콱돨稜삔多폅乖돨슝쪄
I'm going to have to remove myself from the situation
乖돤먀쏨잼역侶쟁
and go sit in the hallway.
혼浬읜쓰麟寧삔랏
Can you come with me? You have a very calming presence.
콱옵鹿톈淪乖찐? 凜槨콱唐蘆잤쓰돨폭醴
Thank you. So few people think that about me.
剋剋 섯빎청唐훙侶척팀송乖돨
But I should stay with Max.
뎃乖狼톈淪Max
No, I got this handled. You can have her.
꼇극 侶쟁乖멥땍 콱혼톈劒걸
This is the last time you give me to someone.
侶角콱離빈寧늴겉乖횻못깎훙
Max, your tart was excellent.
Max 콱돨彊벎軍깰隣돤붤봤
The problem was your attitude.
뎃狂痙놔瞳콱돨檄똑裂
You showed no passion of wanting to be in this school.
콱청唐깊君놔拳狼윱侶쟁欺構돨훑헙
And that is why you didn't get in.
杰鹿乖꼇쩌혤콱돨
It seemed like you didn't want it.
콱慨빎깻꼇拳윱
No, no, no, that's just my attitude.
꼇꼇꼇 侶앎角乖돨檄똑
I act like I don't want anything
乖깊君돤轟杰館
because I never got anything I wanted.
角凜槨乖닒윱돤꼇돕菱성拳狼돨
But I do want to go to this school
뎃乖횅茄옷寡윱侶쟁欺構
more than I've ever wanted anything.
궐乖닒품돨컸硅옷寡뫘속퓻죠
It's my fantasy and my dream,
侶角乖돨瀏헹 角乖돨촘拳
and please stop making me use these horrible, horrible words!
뻘唐깎疼궉乖綱놔侶硅폅샷튄명댓돨늦刀!
Just let me in, okay?
쩌혤乖걸 봤찐?
Okay.
봤돨
Wait, for real?
된된 廬돨찐?
Yes.
角돨
I needed to see if your passion was as good as your pastry
乖돤였였콱돨훑헙角뤠宅콱돨軍깰谿된敲놔
And you just showed me it was.
횔빈콱蕨乖聯츠죄 횅茄흔늪
I'm thrilled to have you on board, chef.
寮놜 乖붤멕菫콱속흙乖쳬
Thanks, chef.
剋剋콱 寮놜
Bebe is having a panic attack and needs to hold her lemon.
Bebe돨쑵왜璉랙鱗 劒狼壞遼劒돨퀴초
Has anyone seen her lemon?
唐强였돕劒돨퀴초찐?
Caroline, he let me in. I'm going to pastry school.
Caroline 儉쩌혤乖죄 乖狼멤듐欺湳죄!
Everybody has to call me "chef" now!
君瞳댕소떼돤싻乖寮놜죄!
You did it, chef!
콱냥묘죄 寮놜!
You're going to the pastry school from the brochure!
콱狼돕忌눈꿍丹돨멤듐欺叫欺構죄!
Aren't you glad I looked at your porn?
콱붤헤妗乖쇱꿴죄콱돨뼝蝎걸?
We're roommates. Both single. Quelle surprise.
乖쳬角杆堂 떼角데 雷棍걸
So Max, once you fill out these,
Max 된콱겉侶硅栗죕輕봤裂빈
You will be officially enrolled.
앎옵鹿攣駕흙欺죄
And of course we will need your tuition check.
뎠횔콱뻘돤겉欺롤連튿못乖쳬
Yup. $3,000. It's a lot for us.
봤돨 힛푤댕捏 옵廬뱍뭘돨
But if we make some cutbacks, 1/2-ply toilet paper.
뎃怜狼乖쳬鍵숑역連 꿈杰珂怜痰곕쌔꿈笭
Who am I kidding? No toilet paper, diner napkins.
乖綱揆돨 꿈笭 꽜쏀떼꼇콘痰죄
No, tuition is 24,000.
꼇 欺롤角좃拱愷푤쳄禱
But the brochure said $3,000 a year.
뎃角忌눈꿍충畇淪角寧쾨힛푤가
You misread it. It's $3,000 a unit.
콱였댄죄 角寧퍅힛푤
There is eight units per year. 24,000.
뎃寧쾨唐검퍅 杰鹿悧묾角좃拱愷푤쳄禱
It costs $24,000? We can't pay that.
狼좃拱愷푤? 乖쳬마꼇폅
Oh, my god, now I'm never gonna be able to come here
莖가 侶苟乖꼇콘윱侶쟁欺構죄
and I just admitted I wanted to!
랍乖먼꼽뻘넓훰죄菱성붤拳윱!
I take back everything I ever said about wanting anything.
乖狼澗쀼먼꼽菱성綱돨컸硅옷寡
Max, you can't just storm out.
Max 콱꼇콘앎侶湳閘癎랍혼
Your face can't just storm out!
콱돨졌꼽꼇콘閘癎랍혼!
Look, I will do anything for that girl to go to this school.
乖毒雷隣훨부慤 윱묩劒侶쟁欺構
In exchange for tuition, I could work in the office.
乖옵鹿瞳곗무杆묏鱗 鹿늪슥뻣欺롤
Bebe clearly needs someone to help take the pressure off.
鞫횔Bebe矜狼唐훙곤劒롸덫箕제
and who better than a mentally stable
랍할뻘唐强돨예箕콘제삔궐
Wharton graduate like myself?
乖侶몸怪뛰欺牘귄撚돨훙퓻켱?
But I'll do anything.
꼇법 乖痂척떼毒雷맴
I'll even wash your floors, okay?
乖逞옵鹿곤콱求뒈겼 봤찐?
Although I'm sure there's something better than that.
꼇법乖횅땍唐硅묏鱗삔궐侶몸퓻寧듐
But if you need me to wash the floors,
뎃흔벎콱矜狼乖求뒈겼돨뺐
I will wash the floors.
乖冷毒雷求뒈겼
Really would prefer to do anything else,
뎃乖뫘拳맴듐깎돨묏鱗
but I'll do it, 'cause I'll do anything
뎃앎炬角求뒈겼乖冷맴 槨죄劒
to get her into this school.
乖痂척떼毒雷隣
Please no floors.
헝꼇狼횻乖求뒈겼
Okay, I will talk it over with my staff
봤걸 乖삔뫄逃묏좆寧苟
and I will let you know.
헝쓰빅繫列
Oh, no, no.
꼇契
I've seen what happens
乖綠쒔숨街죄
when you give people the "I'll let you know."
콱컸얌"쓰빅繫列"삔唐痂척써벎
I'm not going anywhere until you let me know to my face.
乖컴떼꼇혼 뇜렷콱뎠충繫列乖
With your face. Your beautiful, beautiful face.
痰콱컸蠟졌 컸蠟剛폭轟궐돨졌
Max, we're not poor enough?
Max 乖쳬뻘꼇뭘헨찐?
You're starting a hobo trash fire in our apartment?
콱뻘瞳童쳬무櫂쟁폅직읫볶돨윕샐삽뚜?
Yup. I'm burning my porn and pastry school brochure.
角돨 乖瞳菱성돨뼝蝎뵨멤듐欺叫忌눈꿍
You know, all my fantasies.
侶角乖홍꼬돨뼙拳
If I learned anything in life
狼角삶鄧싱貴乖痂척
it's that nothing's more flammable than my dreams.
컸앎角청痂척궐乖돨촘拳뫘휭弄뺏槨뿍쐬
Are those my slipper socks in there?
컸角乖돨糾昆찐?
Yeah, those needed to die too.
角돨 侶몸冷극伎쁑딜
Well, while you were in our living room
봤걸 뎠콱瞳童쳬돨와戒
hosting a burning man festival,
앨契삽훙쌘裂珂
I was at the pastry school getting us
乖홱瞳멤듐欺叫쟁못童쳬
a work-study arrangement.
轢혤寧몸곕묏곕뗍돨샙삔
And...
횔빈...
You're going to pastry school.
콱옵鹿혼멤듐欺叫죄
No way!
廬돨솝돨!
Here you go. Your school uniform.
못콱 侶角콱돨叫륩
This is where my name's gonna go!
鹿빈乖돨츰俚앎季瞳侶쟁
My chef name, conchita bonfire.
乖돨寮놜츰 "횝걸 慣랬벌훙"
Thank you for this.
剋剋콱
And for everything.
鹿섟콱杰隣돨寧학
You don't have to thank me.
콱痰꼇淪剋乖
'Cause with your new skills I'm gonna use you
凜槨乖鹿빈狼적痰콱돨劤세콘
like Kim uses Kanye.
앎獗쏜·엥덖적痰劒일무
Or kanye uses kim. I'm not sure which of them is winning.
棠샀諒角劒일무적痰劒 乖꼇列돛儉젤强돤樓죄
What kind of work-study arrangement did you make for me?
콱槨乖轢혤죄痂척湳돨곕묏곕뗍가?
It's more of a work-study arrangement for us.
페茄侶角乖쳬젤寧폅곕묏곕뗍
I'll be working in the office helping out Bebe,
乖狼혼곗무杆못Bebe곤챈
so I'm working, you're studying.
杰鹿乖묏鱗 콱欺構
You're working at my school? Mom!
콱狼瞳乖돨欺叫묏鱗? 乖돨항쿤가!